export const quiz = {
  
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        'Which is the county 032?',
      choices: ['Nyeri', 'Nakuru', 'Samburu', 'Narok'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Nakuru',
    },
    {
      question:
        'Who is the current cabinet secretary for the National Treasury?',
      choices: ['Njuguna Ndungu', 'Henry Rotich', 'Ababu Namwamba', 'Julius Korir'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Njuguna Ndungu',
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which is the largest county in Kenya?',
      choices: [
        'Marsabit',
        'Kiambu',
        'Garissa',
        'Turkana',
      ],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Turkana',
    },
    {
      question: 'Give the approximate population of Nairobi County?',
      choices: ['4 Million', '3 Million', '3.5 Million', '2 Million'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '4 Million',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which county boarders Kenya to the East?',
      choices: ['Uganda', 'Somalia', 'Ethiopia', 'South Sudan'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Somalia',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is not a Manchester United player?',
      choices: ['Cavani', 'Rashford', 'Fred', 'Martial'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Cavani',
    },
    {
      question: 'Where was the world cup 2022 hosted?',
      choices: ['Saudi Arabia', 'Qatar', 'Dubai', 'France'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Qatar',
    },
    {
      question: 'Pangaea existed?',
      choices: ['About 100 thousand years ago', 'About 5 million years ago', 'About 250 million years ago', 'In the past and still exists today'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'About 250 million years ago',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which town is immediately after Westlands from Nairobi CBD?',
      choices: ['Uthiru', 'Kangemi', 'Kinoo', 'Kabete'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Kangemi',
    },
    {
      question: 'How old is Taylor Swift?',
      choices: ['36 years', '31 years', '33 years', '34 years'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '33 years',
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the last year Manchester United won the English Premier League?',
      choices: ['2013', '2016', '2019', '2014'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '2013',
    },
    {
      question: 'What year was google started?',
      choices: ['1998', '2004', '2008', '2010'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '1998',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one of the following is not an American state?',
      choices: ['Denver', 'Ohio', 'Wyoming', 'Alabama'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Denver',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many countries are there in the world?',
      choices: ['206', '195', '178', '115'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '195',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the capital city of England?',
      choices: ['Paris', 'London', 'Berlin', 'Madrid'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'London',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one of these regions is not located in Nakuru County?',
      choices: ['Kivumbini', 'Lanet', 'Flamingo', 'Miritini'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Miritini',
    },
  ],
}
